mangatutorials.com 2016-12-03

# Manga Tutorials » Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at the following URL – http://www.mangatutorials.com/contact-manga-tutorials/

At MangaTutorials.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by MangaTutorials.com and how it is used.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### LOG FILES:

Like many other Web sites, MangaTutorials.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

MangaTutorials.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MangaTutorials.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to MangaTutorials.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on MangaTutorials.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

MangaTutorials.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MangaTutorials.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
